UGWU COLLINS

Frontend Developer

STRENGTHS



Coding Expert

Proficient in HTML, CSS, JS,REACT



Problem Solver

Innovative approach to challenges



Team Player

Excellent collaboration skills

SKILLS

HTML

CSS

JavaScript

Responsive Design

React.js

ACHIEVEMENTS



Website Performance

Improved by 35% at Tech Company A



Page Load Time

Reduced by 30% at Tech Company B



Rising Star Award

Received at Tech Company C

INDUSTRY EXPERTISE

Front-end develoment

SUMMARY

Passionate Frontend Developer with a knack for creating intuitive and highperforming web applications.

I excel at motivating, & developing teams of less experienced developers. Ready to bring coding expertise and innovative problem-solving skills to and solve the challenges ofthe company.

EXPERIENCE

Frontend Developer

Tech Company B

= 2021 - 2023 ♀ N

Nigeria, Enugu

Worked on various web development projects

- · Contributed to the development of websites
- Reduced page load time on 10 client websites by 30% through a number of optimization techniques. Became the company expert on load time, web vitals

Junior Frontend Developer

TECH COMPANY

= 2020 - 2023

Nigeria, Enugu

Assisted in the development of web applications

- · Worked on web development projects
- Improved website accessibility
- · Received 'Rising Star' award for outstanding performance

EDUCATION

Bachelor of Science in Computer Science

University of Nigeria

= 2016 - 2020

♀ Nigeria, Enugu

OPEN-SOURCE WORK

TodoistClone

A clone of the popular to-do list application, Todoist. Built with React .